Guide to the Rice University Early Land Deeds, Contracts and Related Records, 1830-1969 UA 222
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Oversize drawers, 144192 (Drawer 129-131)
  - Delinquent tax notices, Fayette Co., 1917 (from box 9, folder 5), 144408 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - Plat - J.P. McFarland League, Fayette Co., 1917 (from box 9, folder 5), 144409 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - 3 plats: Hagler Survey Ellis Co., 1918 Map - location of levee across Rice Institute land in Ellis County Improvement District #3; Calculation of Hagler Survey by J.W. Martin, county surveyor, 1918 (from box 8, folder 10), 144410 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - Plat - Ellis County Levee Improvement District No. 3 (from box 8, folder 9), 144411 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - Blueprint - Dallas-Hutchins Pike and H & T.C.R.R. property in Dallas Co., 1922 (from box 8, folder 5), 144412 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - Hand drawn sketch - Rice Institute property near Hamilton Rd., Dallas Co., undated (from box 8, folder 8), 144413 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - Blueprint - Land belonging to Thomas Brothers, Dallas Co., 1922 (from box 8, folder 5, sub-folder 2), 144414 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - Blueprint - Dallas County near Miller Switch, 1913 (from box 8, folder 5), 144415 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - 2 Blueprints: Plot showing Rice House and Oliver Map for proposed new Millers Ferry Bridge, 1910 (from box 8, folder 1), 144416 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - Deed from S.M. Swenson to S.B Crittenden Jr., 1859; Land grant to S.M. Swenson - signed by Gov. Houston, 1861 (from box 7, folder 22), 144417 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - Land grant - Decatur Daniels (from box 6, folder 8), 144419 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - Blueprint - Lutcher and More pine holdings in Louisiana and Texas, 1913 (from box 2, folder 2), 144445 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - Map, W.C. Sypert Survey (From box 18, folder 14), 144352 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 2)
  - Land Grant - J.B. Pier, 1890 (from box 11, folder 1, sub-folder 5), 144404 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Inventory of appraisement, 1914 (from box 10, folder 2, folder 1), 144406 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint, unobstructed easement, 1939 (from box 14, folder 12), 144380 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - 2 blueprints: Unobstructed easement, 1939 Plat showing block McGregor's Blodgett Addition (from box 14, folder 11), 144381 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - 2 blueprints: 10' unobstructed easement in A.C. Reynolds Survey, 1940 Plat showing rice Institute land between Westheimer and San Felipe (from box 14, folder 9), 144382 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - 4 Blueprints: Proposed opening of road from Westheimer to Alief Houston Rd 10' ditch easement 10' unobstructed easement, 1953 Property purchased from Houston Realty Syndicate for right of way, 1928 (from box 14, folder 7), 144383 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - Survey of Rice Institute property West of Louisiana St and North of Jefferson St., 1923 (from box 13, folder 1), 144385 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Map, Post Oak Rd., Westheimer to Alief Rd., 1950 (from box 14, folder 7), 144386 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Ben J. Smith Subdivision no. 2 street layout (2) (from box 13, folder 19), 144387 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - 4 blueprints: Survey of lot 5, B.J. Smith subdivision of great lot 2, O. Smith Survey, 1926 (2) Ben J. Smith Subdivision no. 2, 1913 (2) (from box 13, folder 19), 144388 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - 2 blueprints: Showing 26 4/10 acres of a portion of lot no. 2 of the Morse Subdivision, 1911 Showing survey of Meineke Tract and Goar Tract in lot no. 3...., 1924 (from box 13, folder 18), 144389 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - new survey, Louisiana St. property and Fredericks Addition, 1923 (3) (from box 13, folder 17), 144390 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Sketch showing Rice Institute acreage out of the O. Smith Survey, 1916 (from box 13, folder 17), 144391 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - widening of Kuykendahl Rd, J.C. Donally Survey, Harris Co., 1925 (from box 13, folder 14), 144392 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint sketch in the J. Reinerman Survey showing Rice Institute lands in lot 2...., 1911 (2) (from box 13, folder 12), 144393 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - 10.18 acres of first survey (from box 13, folder 3), 144394 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - section through to Texas Warehouse (from box 12, folder 7), 144395 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - part of the Doziel 928 acres in the A.C. Reynolds Survey, 1920 (from box 12, folder 6), 144396 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Redemption receipt for taxes paid, 1932; Braeswood Corporation - title timeline and chart, 1932; Plat showing survey of McNee tract and Elizabeth Clark Tract, 1929 (from box 12, folder 4), 144397 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Refunding certificates (2) - #608 and #609, 1900 (from box 11, folder 5), 144402 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - plat of block No. 51 bordered by Texas Ave., Prairie Ave., Crawford St and LaBranch St., 1926 (from box 15, folder 1), 144379 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - Memorial Drive Right of way from N. Shepherd Dr. to memorial park, 1931 (from box 15, folder 31), 144371 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - Germantown addition, 1862 (from box 16, folder 1), 144368 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Sketch - Rice lands in West portion of Bringhurst Subdivision, 1911 (from box 15, folder 31), 144370 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Rice Institute - 106.7 acre tract in lot 2 of the Bringhurst Subdivision, 1926 (from box 15, folder 31), 144369 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Sketch - Hildebrandt's Enclosure, 1915 (from box 16, folder 9), 144367 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Subdivision map, 1915 (from box 16, folder 10), 144366 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint, contour map (from box 16, folder 10), 144365 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Topographic cross section map (from box 16, folder 10), 144364 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Map - property on Buffalo Bayou near Greenwood Cemetery, 1916 (from box 16, folder 11), 144361 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Block map (from box 16, folder 10), 144363 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Sanitary sewer easement, 90 acres, Afton Oaks area, 1953 (2 prints) (from box 16, folder 42), 144355 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - Oak Estates Subdivision for S.N. Adams, 1947 (from box 16, folder 37), 144357 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Negative print - map showing Kinkaid School property (from box 16, folder 34), 144358 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Map - proposed easement for South side sanitary sewer trunk line, 1947 (from box 16, folder 32), 144359 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Map - Greater Houston and San Antonio railroad near Childress Blvd, 1944 (from box 16, folder 31), 144360 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Linen map - 16 acres of W.R. Baker property, 1902 (from box 16, folder 10), 144362 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - Ben Andrews property, 1937 (from box 15, folder 31), 144372 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - Memorial Drive, 1928 (from box 15, folder 31), 144373 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - sketch in the Reinerman League showing Rice Institute properties, 1911 (from box 15, folder 31), 144374 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Plat showing land - M. Sandel to Rice Institute (from box 15, folder 26), 144375 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - showing land exchanged (from box 15, folder 26), 144376 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - plat showing encroachment of Richmond Place on William M. Rice Institute tract, 1932 (from box 15, folder 8), 144377 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Plat showing right of way at Donnelly Road (from box 15, folder 3), 144378 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Land Grant - John M. Swisher, 1890 (from box 11, folder 1, sub-folder 5), 144403 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - sketch in the Northern one half in the Elizabeth League (from box 18, folder 13), 144353 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprints (2) - John R. Black Survey (from box 18, folder 16, sub-folder 3), 144350 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Maps (3) - Westmoreland Farms (Bellaire), 1911 (from box 19, folder 1), 144349 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint - 1,00 acre tract, part of Westmoreland Farms, 1909 (2) (From box 19, folder 1, sub-folder 3), 144348 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Map, Westmoreland Farms, amended first subdivision, 1911 (from box 19, folder 1, sub-folder 3), 144347 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint - Eastern portion of J.R. Black Survey, 1915 (from box 19, folder 4), 144346 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Maps, Westmoreland Farms, amended first subdivision, 1911 (2) (from box 19, folder 5), 144345 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Map of Westmoreland Farm amended first subdivision, 1911 (with sketch of South part of Brown survey attached) (from box 19, folder 5), 144344 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint - Jonathan R. Black Survey, Harris Co., 1916 (from box 19, folder 5), 144343 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint - map of Westmoreland Farms, 1922 (from box 19, folder 5), 144342 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint - map showing Westmoreland Farms in relation to Houston, Texas, 1910 (from box 19, folder 5), 144341 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint - map of Westmoreland Farms, 1911 (from box 19, folder 5), 144340 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Map of 2nd subdivision, Westmoreland Farms, 1912 (from box 19, folder 5), 144339 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint - Blocks 6 & 7 of 1st subdivision, Westmoreland Farms, 1911 (from box 19, folder 5), 144338 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint - plat of block 25 amended first subdivision, Westmoreland Farms, 1917 (from box 20, folder 1), 144337 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Redemption receipt and copy, 1922 (from box 21, folder 3), 144336 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Map - working sketch of Irion Co., 1921; Blueprint - blocks 27 & 28 H&TC Railroad, Irion Co., 1902 (from box 21, folder 11), 144334 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint and map showing resurvey of portion of North 1/2 of John James Survey, 1917 (from box 22, folder 1), 144332 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Land Grant - Lurana Allen (from box 22, folder 3), 144331 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Land Grant - Andrew Smythe (Smith) (from box 22, folder 6), 144330 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Map & blueprint of 3 Smith (Smythe) surveys, 1917 (from box 22, folder 8), 144329 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Map & blueprint - part of Peter B. Pry Survey, 1917 (from box 22, folder 8), 144328 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Land Grant - Robert Williamson, et al. (from box 22, folder 9), 144327 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprints (5) - Resurvey of part of Smith Survey (from box 22, folder 8), 144326 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Map - resurvey of part of Smith Survey (from box 22, folder 8), 144325 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprints (3) - Traverse of Neches River front on Smith Survey (from box 22, folder 8), 144324 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Log scale (from box 23, folder 2), 144323 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprints (2) - Survey in Jasper Co. for the William M. Rice Institute (from box 23, folder 7), 144320 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint - showing proposed route of camp 5 tram, 1916 (from box 23, folder 8), 144319 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - 2 Land Grants: Washington Mitchell, Jasper Co., 1881 William Morgan, Jasper Co., 1859 (from box 23, folder 10), 144317 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Blueprint - P.W. Rose Survey, 1903 (from box 17, folder 29), 144354 (Map-drawer 129, Folder 4)
  - Plot, Silas Woods Survey (from box 26, folder 4), 144307 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Plot, David Frost Survey (from box 26, folder 2), 144308 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Plot of the George W. Louder, 370 acre survey, Lee Co. (from box 26, folder 1), 144309 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Plot - Leon Co. surveys (from box 25, folder 9), 144310 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - 2 land grant documents for Lampasas Co.: 640 acres signed by Gov. Davis, 1898 640 acres signed by Gov. Leake, 1875 (from box 25, folder 8), 144311 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Land grant for William M. Rice for 640 acres in Lampasas Co., signed by Gov. Hogg, 1891 (from box 25, folder 8), 144312 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Land grant for William M. Rice for 640 acres in Lampasas Co., signed by Gov. Davis, 1873 (from box 25, folder 8), 144313 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - subdivision of League No. 334, Harrison Co. school land (from box 24, folder 4), 144315 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map, Burleson Survey, Lee Co., 1917 (from box 26, folder 14), 144305 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - map showing paving to be done in Mexia, Tx, 1922 (from box 27, folder 11), 144304 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - David Lane Survey, Marion Co., 1938 (from box 28, folder 3), 144303 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Land Grant, 1920 (from box 28, folder 8), 144300 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - map of Robinson, Jones and Stansbury Surveys, Montgomery Co., 1920 (from box 28, folder 8), 144299 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - map showing land taken by right of way for state highway 35 (from box 28, folder 14), 144298 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - Texas Highway Dept. sketch: Easement for Caney Creek Channel change @ Hwy 59, Montgomery Co., 1946 (from box 29, folder 5), 144297 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - application for easement, approximately 8 miles East of Conroe, Texas (from box 29, folder 16), 144296 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - concerning survey and timber estimate of Montgomery lands, East of Conroe, Texas for the William M. Rice Institute (from box 29, folder 16, sub-folder 2), 144295 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprints (2) - gas pipeline crossing (from box 29, folder 16, sub-folder 3), 144294 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Land grant for 160 acres to Edmund A. Blank in Montgomery Co. signed by Gov. Lubbock, 1863 (from box 29, folder 16, sub-folder 4), 144293 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - Easement sketch, William M. Rice Institute, J.E. Lewis Survey, Montgomery Co., 1928 (from box 29, folder 16, sub-folder 5), 144292 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - Easement covering right of way across portion of A.P. Fredericks Survey for the telephone and telegraph line (from box 29, folder 17, sub-folder 4), 144291 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - Easement covering right of way for gas transmission line across A.P. Fredericks Survey, 1951 (from box 29, folder 17, sub-folder 6), 144290 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - Showing 450 acres of South Side of Bennett Blake League, Montgomery Co., 1924 (from box 29, folder 17, sub-folder 7), 144289 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - Survey of tie in proposed railway spur, Navarro Co. (from box 30, folder 2), 144288 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map - Rice Institute land on John White and John Choate Surveys, Navarro Co., 1917 (from box 30, folder 7), 144287 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map - John Choate Survey, 1917 (from box 30, folder 8), 144286 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - 4 Blueprints: Resurvey of portion of original Polly Youngblood Survey, 1917 (2) Resurvey and estimate on 150 acres of Polly Youngblood Tract, 1917 Survey of 278.5 acres in Polly Youngblood Tract, 1917 (from box 31, folder 7), 144285 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - 3 Plats: Resurvey of portion of Polly Youngblood Survey, 1917 Resurvey and estimate on 150 acres of Polly Youngblood Tract, 1917 Survey of 278.5 acres in Polly Youngblood Tract, 1917 (from box 31, folder 8), 144284 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map and Blueprint - Resurvey of P.D. Moyer Survey, 400 acres with estimate (from box 32, folder 1), 144283 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprints (3) - survey and resurvey of P.D. Moyer Survey of 400 acres (from box 32, folder 1), 144282 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - partial Resurvey of M.B. Lewis Military Survey of 320 acres, Newton Co. (from box 32, folder 10, sub-folder 3), 144281 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map - Thomas Tanner Survey, Newton Co., 1908 (from box 32, folder 12, sub-folder 3), 144280 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map of Sabine Co., 1879 (from box 34, folder 4), 144279 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprints (2) - East Texas and Gulf Railway in Tyler Co., 1917 (from box 35, folder 15), 144277 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map - report on Tyler County lands to A.B. Cohen, 1922 (from box 36, folder 2), 144276 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map - proposed transmission line crossing Rice Institute land in Tyler Co., 1930 (from box 36, folder 4, sub-folder 3), 144273 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - easement sketch Lumberton-Colmes Neil line #68, Tyler Co., 1930 (from box 36, folder 4, sub-folder 3), 144272 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - proposed transmission line crossing Rice Institute lands in Tyler Co., 1930 (from box 36, folder 4, sub-folder 3), 144271 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprints (2) - Plat of proposed right of way crossing, Tyler Co., 1944 (from box 36, folder 4, sub-folder 6), 144269 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - anchor points for telephone line along Warren-Spurger Rd., Tyler Co. (from box 36, folder 4, sub-folder 7), 144268 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprints (2) - showing right of way for Hillister-Spurger Rd. (from FM 1013), Tyler Co. (from box 36, folder 4, sub-folder 9), 144267 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - gas line right of way to serve SE Hillister gas unit no. 1, 1951 (from box 36, folder 5, sub-folder 1), 144266 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprints (2) - plats showing right of way (from box 36, folder 5 sub-folder 3), 144265 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprints (2) - right of way for Atlantic Pipeline Co. through Rice owned land (from box 36, folder 5, sub-folder 5), 144264 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map - J.M. Stephens League, Waller Co., 1907 (from box 37, folder 14), 144263 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Blueprint - J.M. Stephens Survey, Waller Co. (from box 37, folder 14), 144262 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map - J.M. Stephens Survey and surrounding surveys, Waller Co. (from box 37, folder 14), 144261 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Land Grant to Jonathan M. Stephens, 1856 (from box 37, folder 14), 144259 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map - gravity gradients, J.M. Stephens Survey, Waller Co. (from box 37, folder 14), 144260 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Plat showing 4 lots (3-6) in Daniel Lloyd Survey (from box 37, folder 18), 144258 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Map - Thomas Beedy Survey, 1907 (from box 24, folder 5), 144314 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 1)
  - Statements, insurance cancellations, 1928 (from box 58, folder 4, sub-folder 5), 144237 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 2)
  - Schedule of statements, United States Fidelity & Guaranty Co., 1914 (from box 58, folder 4, sub-folder 1), 144238 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 2)
  - Expiring insurance listing, 1932 (from box 58, folder 3), 144240 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 2)
  - Schedules of fire insurance policies, 1936-1938 (6) (from box 58, folder 1), 144241 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 2)
  - Data of valves contents of Rice Institute buildings (3) (from box 57, folder 6), 144242 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 2)
  - Statements of additional insurance, 1929 (from box 58, folder 3, sub-folder 1), 144239 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 2)
  - Blueprints (2) - Basement and first floor of kitchen and refrigeration equipment, residential hall, 1912 (from box 41, folder 2, sub-folder 1), 144247 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 2)
  - Blueprint - map showing roads and walks on Rice Institute campus, 1911 (from box 40, folder 2, sub-folder 1), 144250 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 2)
  - Blueprint - revised layout, drains and temporary sewers, 1911 (from box 39, folder 3, sub-folder 2), 144254 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 2)
  - Blueprint - improvements of grounds, 1913 (from box 39, folder 4), 144253 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 2)
  - Deed, Heinrich Leverkuhne to August Proetzelo, 1866 (from box 59, folder 1), 144236 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Plat, Joseph S, Rice Military Addition, John Reinerman Survey, 1910 (from box 59, folder 1), 144234 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Map - tract disputes, Reinerman Survey (from box 59, folder 1), 144233 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - tract disputes, Reinerman Survey (from box 59, folder 1), 144232 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - old Taylor School site, Louisiana @ Clay, 1924 (from box 59, folder 5), 144231 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - Rice Institute property, West of Louisiana and North of Jefferson, 1923 (from box 59, folder 5), 144230 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - services and gas lines, Louisiana @ Leland, 1914 (from box 59, folder 5), 144229 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - block 298, Louisiana @ Clay, 1922 (from box 59, folder 5), 144228 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Plat - location of easement, Rice Institute stadium, 1951 (from box 62, folder 4), 144210 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Improvement Certificate to Eureka Paving Co., 1914 (from box 59, folder 5), 144226 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Sketch, Rice Institute acreage out of O. Smith Survey, 1916 (from box 59, folder 5), 144225 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Map - Pease St. from Main to Louisiana St, 1914 (from box 59, folder 5), 144224 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Map - Institute property to Louisiana @ Bell (from box 59, folder 5), 144223 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - showing Rice property on Louisiana (from box 59, folder 5), 144222 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Map of proposed drainage ditch through campus, 1924 (from box 61, folder 8), 144217 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - USGS Topographical map of Bellaire Quadrangle (from box 61, folder 8), 144218 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - 2 Blueprints: Plat of Sunset Rd. between Rice Institute and Shady Side Estates, 1918 Proposed revised alignment - Sunset Rd. and Rice Blvd., 1923 (from box 62, folder 2), 144214 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Brochure/map of Southampton Place, 1923 (from box 62, folder 4), 144211 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Blueprint - proposed 8" water main for the Rice Institute, 1928 (from box 62, folder 4), 144209 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Blueprints (7) - Easements and storm sewers for right of way through institute campus (from box 62, folder 5), 144208 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Blueprints (2) - land exchanges (from box 60, folder 1, sub-folder 2), 144221 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Blueprints (2) - survey of Taylor School site, 1914 (from box 59, folder 5), 144227 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Blueprints (4) - tract disputes, Reinerman Survey (from box 59, folder 1), 144235 (Map-drawer 130, Folder 3)
  - Plat - a tract of land containing an area of 79 5/100 acres surveyed per P.L. Guffin of Giddings, Tx (from box 26, folder 10), 144306 (Map-drawer 131, Folder 1)
  - Time line of P.B. Pry Survey, 1917 (from box 23, folder 2), 144322 (Map-drawer 131, Folder 1)
  - P.B. Pry lease (from box 23, folder 2), 144321 (Map-drawer 131, Folder 1)
  - Map of Jones County Texas, 1879 (from box 24, folder 3), 144316 (Map-drawer 131, Folder 1)
  - Land Grant for Jesse Cass Assee signed by Governor Ireland, 1920 (from box 21, folder 10), 144335 (Map-drawer 131, Folder 1)
  - Land Grants (2) to John James, 1870 & 1891 (from box 22, folder 1), 144333 (Map-drawer 131, Folder 1)
  - Plat showing land in Beauregard Parish showing tenancy "exhibit A" (A) (from box 2, folder 10, sub-folder 1), 144433 (Map-drawer 131, Folder 1)
  - Plat showing land in Beauregard Parish showing tenancy "exhibit A" (B) (from box 2, folder 10, sub-folder 1), 144432 (Map-drawer 131, Folder 1)